[
  {
    "title": "Name these European Capital Cities",
    "category": "Geography",
    "creator": "Sam1",
    "instructions": ["Answer in any order you want"],
    "seconds": 180,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "United Kingdom",
        "correct": "London",
        "accepted": []
      },
      {
        "question": "Ireland",
        "correct": "Dublin",
        "accepted": ["Baile Átha Cliath"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Spain",
        "correct": "Madrid",
        "accepted": []
      },
      {
        "question": "Portugal",
        "correct": "Lisbon",
        "accepted": ["Lisboa"]
      },
      {
        "question": "France",
        "correct": "Paris",
        "accepted": []
      },
      {
        "question": "Belgium",
        "correct": "Brussels",
        "accepted": ["Bruxelles", "Brussel"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Netherlands",
        "correct": "Amsterdam",
        "accepted": []
      },
      {
        "question": "Germany",
        "correct": "Berlin",
        "accepted": []
      },
      {
        "question": "Italy",
        "correct": "Rome",
        "accepted": ["Roma"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Greece",
        "correct": "Athens",
        "accepted": []
      },
      {
        "question": "Romania",
        "correct": "Bucharest",
        "accepted": ["București"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Sweden",
        "correct": "Stockholm",
        "accepted": []
      },
      {
        "question": "Austria",
        "correct": "Vienna",
        "accepted": ["Wien"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Switzerland",
        "correct": "Bern",
        "accepted": ["Berna", "Berne"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Ukraine",
        "correct": "Kyiv",
        "accepted": ["Kiev"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Name the First 10 Prime Numbers",
    "category": "Maths",
    "creator": "Sam2",
    "instructions": [],
    "seconds": 60,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "1.",
        "correct": "2",
        "accepted": ["one"]
      },
      {
        "question": "2.",
        "correct": "3",
        "accepted": ["three"]
      },
      {
        "question": "3.",
        "correct": "5",
        "accepted": ["five"]
      },
      {
        "question": "4.",
        "correct": "7",
        "accepted": ["seven"]
      },
      {
        "question": "5.",
        "correct": "11",
        "accepted": ["eleven"]
      },
      {
        "question": "6.",
        "correct": "13",
        "accepted": ["thirteen"]
      },
      {
        "question": "7.",
        "correct": "17",
        "accepted": ["seventeen"]
      },
      {
        "question": "8.",
        "correct": "19",
        "accepted": ["nineteen"]
      },
      {
        "question": "9.",
        "correct": "23",
        "accepted": ["twenty-three"]
      },
      {
        "question": "10.",
        "correct": "29",
        "accepted": ["twenty-nine"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Answer these European History Questions",
    "category": "History",
    "creator": "Sam3",
    "instructions": ["Surnames are sufficient for names of people"],
    "seconds": 120,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "In which year did World War II begin?",
        "correct": "1939",
        "accepted": ["39"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country gained independence from the UK in 1921?",
        "correct": "Ireland",
        "accepted": ["Republic of Ireland"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Which modern country used to be named 'Bohemia'?",
        "correct": "Czech Republic",
        "accepted": ["Czechia"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first leader of Communist Russia in 1917?",
        "correct": "Vladimir Lenin",
        "accepted": ["Lenin"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Constantinople was a former name of which modern city?",
        "correct": "Istanbul",
        "accepted": []
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was Spain's fascist dictator from 1939-1975?",
        "correct": "Francisco Franco",
        "accepted": ["Franco"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country was under Russian rule from 1809-1917?",
        "correct": "Finland",
        "accepted": []
      },
      {
        "question": "Which small country is situated within Italy? (Two options)",
        "correct": "Vatican City & San Marino",
        "accepted": ["Vatican City", "Vatican", "San Marino", "Marino"]
      }
    ]
  }
]
